CAMILO SIERRA

DATA SCIENTIST & AND IT TECHNICIAN

Brief-Intro

I am a Data Scientist and IT technician with over 4 years of experience working with big and small corporation in multiple projects, building tech solutions and providing a variety of support with multiple technologies.

I started as a commercial communicator and throughout the years I discovered a hidden passion for technology. Since then I have built my professional, and some part of my personal life as well, around the world of technology.

Skills _____

- Python | SQL | Mathematics | Statistics | Linux | Docker | Django | CSS | HTML | JASON | Networking | Windows
- MySQL | Java | VDI | Scripting CSV | LAN | WAN | PHP | Web Development | Bootstrap | Portainer | MacOS
- Azure | UX/UI | SAP | Pytorch | Pandas | Git | GitHub

Experience _____

IT Technician Au. 24, 2022 - Current

Provide technical support to a fast-paced investment firm. Configure CORP networks on personal and company hardware. Maintain and update profiles in Azure company portal. Fix and configure available resources.

- Scripting and automations for repetitive tasks.
- Provide guick and efficient solutions for Wall-Street stock brokers.
- Change, configure & set company hardware resources.

SQL Support Programmer

Tecsvs.com

(Intr) June 2022 - August 2022

Support WMS platforms source code. Assess for incidents and report system failures. Resolve SQL conflicts on remote DBMS Production. Fast-paced solutions.

- Scripting and deploying automations for repetitive tasks.
- RDBMS configurations and support.
- Java scripting and pathing for software processing.

Marketing Specialist

RepublicaDelCacao

June 2019 - Oct.2020

Manage sales, marketing and web incorporations. Ensure a seamless workflow and consistency over retails sales and web marketing target strategies. Meet key performance indexes and metrics.

- Create, develop and execute marketing strategies.
- Create, develop KPIs and reports for Management.
- Coordinate and web structure for consistency and effective marketing.

Fast-Phase work with SAP ticketing system. Customer Support and client relation. .

- SAP Ticketing Fulfillment.
- Multitasking.
- Communication skills.

Volunteering & Projects

LatinArte.ca Oct. 2022 - Jan 2023

Web development and maintenance of all resources for blog and event deployments on the website. Distribution of new content for event monitoring on Wordpress platform.

- Develop and deploy new content to the website.
- Improve speed & UX/UI on wordpress CMS.
- Debugging and patching source code.

Education

Web Dev.

Micro-Bachelors DEC Technical Degree Mathematics & Statistics | <u>LSE</u> | 2023 - jun, 2024 ongoing Computing Support Tech. | <u>Institut Teccart</u> | 2020 - 2022 Commercial Communication | <u>SENA</u> | 2016 | 2019

Soft Skills

- English B2 | Français B1 | Español Native
- Initiative | Active Communication | Dedication | Improvement | Customer Relations | B2B relations
- Customer Support | Clients acquisition